And we can also have dictation, so let me give it my command with dictation actually, right?
So, let me click on this one and allow this time.
Hello u.com, this is my first time using you.
Okay, so I remove it and I start over.
Hello u.com, this is my first experience ever when it comes to using you.
What's wrong with you? What are these that you have added over here?
This is my first time that I'm using you and I wanted to ask you some questions.
So, the first question is that what is the difference between you and the other chatbots that are available out there,
like chatGPT and stuff? And what do you provide, especially, you know?
And the other question that I have is that do you have a voice mode and can you create images and that's all?
Yeah.